<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Deep Learning on Raja Biswas</title>
    <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/tags/deep-learning/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Deep Learning on Raja Biswas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 21:12:08 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rbiswasfc.github.io/tags/deep-learning/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Word Embeddings</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/nlp/word_embeddings/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Nov 2019 21:12:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/nlp/word_embeddings/</guid>
      <description>Summary of word embeddings
 word2vec glove fasttext  import numpy as np  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Mitigation of unintended bias in text classification</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/nlp/jigsaw_bias/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 09 Aug 2019 21:12:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/nlp/jigsaw_bias/</guid>
      <description> Kaggle comprtition organized by Jigsaw Conversation AI. It was second edition of the competion.
Bias Metrics  BPSN SPBN Subgroup  Combined tbc
Mod import numpy as np  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A bottom-up recommender system for travel destinations</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/deepfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 21:11:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/deepfly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Project Status: Active Objective To develop a web based platform that gives personalized recommendations for travel destinations and activities based on user preferences. The recommendations will be accompanied with a list of directly comparable features pertaining to the suggested destinations, such that the user(s) can delve deeper and emerge with a satisfied choice.
To this end, a bottom-up solution algorithm is adopted:
 At the top level, a list of countries are considered Each country contains a list of travel destinations Each destination contains a list of Points Of Interest (POI)  We will predict the scores of the POIs based on user profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Google Compute Engine setup for data science projects</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/tutorial/gce/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 01 Feb 2019 21:12:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/tutorial/gce/</guid>
      <description>Google Compute Engine (GCE) is a component of Google Cloud Platform (GCP), which enables users to launch virtual machines (VMs) on demand. As per the project requirements, VMs can support the use of SSD and GPUs. In this article, I will summarize how to setup a GCE VM for solving data science related problems.
NB: this document is for my future reference.
Steps The process involves the following steps:</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>