<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Raja Biswas</title>
    <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Raja Biswas</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 21:11:12 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://rbiswasfc.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>A bottom-up recommender System for travel destinations</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/deepfly/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Aug 2019 21:11:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/deepfly/</guid>
      <description>&amp;ndash; Project Status: Active Objective To develop a web based platform that gives personalized recommendations for travel destinations and activities based on user preferences. The recommendations will be accompanied with a list of directly comparable features pertaining to the suggested destinations, such that the user(s) can delve deeper and emerge with a satisfied choice.
To this end, a bottom-up solution algorithm is adopted:
 At the top level, a list of countries are considered Each country contains a list of travel destinations Each destination contains a list of Points Of Interest (POI)  We will predict the scores of the POIs based on user profile.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Japan</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/tutorial/gce/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:12:08 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/tutorial/gce/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Nmt</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/machine_translation/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 21:09:48 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/machine_translation/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>National Data Science Challenge 2019 - Shopee</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/ndsc/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Apr 2019 21:10:24 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/posts/projects/ndsc/</guid>
      <description>Shopee, an e-commerce platform headquartered in Singapore, organized the National Data Science Challenge during February-March 2019, highlighting Singapore’s emphasis on driving the digital economy and the use of big data. I actively participated in this competition to apply machine learning skills for a real world commercial application. It was an enriching experience, with a bonus that my team (NYRS) secured the third position in the competition leaderboard. This article summarizes steps followed to solve the problem.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About me</title>
      <link>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2019 21:00:12 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rbiswasfc.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>Creative, dynamic and self-driven researcher with expertise in problem identification, extracting data-driven insights and delivering efficient solutions. Keen interest in executing end-to-end machine learning projects to develop cutting edge AI applications. 5+ years of programming experience with strong proficiency in building deep learning models for computer vision and natural language processing.
I am looking for opportunities in data science. Please feel free to get in touch with me at rajabiswas92@outlook.com or on social media (see the links on the sidebar).</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>